"There we go.
What a good baby."
"What a good baby boy."
"Yes. Yes, I know.
You like that butterfly? Huh?"
I could be late again.
I'm gonna leave a check
for this week in the kitchen, okay?
Okay.
Hey.
Now you repeat after me,
little man--
I will not throw food
at Tina again.
Well, I tried.
Oh, don't worry.
He's a good boy.
Like his father. Here we go.
Want a piece of cracker?
Yes.
I'm Agent Jurmain.
This is Agent Weber.
We're gonna be your ride today.
- Come on.
- Hey, rules are rules.
He's a cop.
Not in front of his kid.
All right. Let's go.
- Agent LaRoche.
- Lisbon.
Jane.
Hmm, yes. The man
that watches the watchmen.
How's tricks?
You tell me.
Oh, you'll get nothing from me, copper.
I'm no rat.
My team and I will cooperate
in any way we can.
We've got nothing to hide.
Just better things
to do with our day.
Ah. The man of the hour.
Excuse me.
You're excused.
If I don't like
what you have to say
you could walk out of this room
charged with murder.
Do you understand that?
Yes.
Very well.
Let's begin with your arrival
in Carson Springs a week ago.
I got the call
around 3:00 in the morning.
It was a shooting death
on the edge of town.
"I arrived about 5:00 a.m."
"Jane and Lisbon were
around 20 minutes behind."
What have we got?
Victim's name is Andy Huff.
Found three shotgun shells
over there.
Nice ride.
It's perfectly restored
except for the pellet holes.
- Does he live nearby?
- He lives downtown.
He's a barber.
Owns his own shop.
It's a strange place to stop.
Yeah, the local P.D. says the city
has a pretty big drug trade.
Couple big gangs run it.
The Overtons and the, uh...
Low-Riders
have the town split in two.
- Doesn't look like a gang member.
- He's got no record, either.
Customer maybe?
Drug deal gone wrong?
- We should ask the other guy.
- The other guy?
What other guy?
A towel's missing.
Our towel thief.
Another victim, or it's the shooter?
Beats me.
We've got a wounded man
who's left the scene.
Alert the local hospitals to be
on the lookout for a gunshot victim.
The attack was hours ago.
Whoever it was
could be miles from here.
Wounded people,
they don't wanna run.
They, uh, wanna hide.
This is the California Bureau
of Investigation!
We know you're in there!
"Go away!"
"I got a gun, and I'll shoot!"
Uh, I'm gonna be back here.
I'm coming in!
Rigsby!
Throw out your weapon.
Now!
You go straight to hell.
Dad?
What the hell did you do, Dad?
Hello to you, too, son.
"We have dealt
with your father before."
Last time, I felt that you
weren't being honest with me.
Your father is a criminal.
A violent felon.
"Smuggling. Narcotics.
Manslaughter."
- "Yes."
- "One-time Sergeant at Arms"
- "of the Iron Gods motorcycle gang."
- "Yes."
"Served time in Lompoc, San Quentin"
- "Pelican Bay."
- "Yes."
"Did you know that he was living
in the Carson Springs area?"
"I heard he'd moved.
Didn't know where."
Had your relationship
with your father changed?
What relationship?
- How is he?
- He's stabilized.
We put four units
of blood in him.
He's got a couple dozen
shotgun pellets in him.
Most of them
shouldn't be a problem
unless he walks
through a metal detector.
- Most of them?
- There's a pellet close to his heart
lodged in his pericardium.
There's a chance it could fall out.
If it does, it could cause
cardiac arrest or a stroke.
Well, can you get to it?
Open-heart surgery
is too great a risk
especially in his condition.
Hopefully, scar tissue will cover it
and he'll be fine.
- Is there anything that can help?
- Quiet life, low heart rate.
He should invest
in a good easy chair.
Avoid excitement.
Smoking. Drinking. Hard living.
Great.
- Uh, can I ask him a few questions?
- Yeah. Both of us.
How do you feel?
Well, they got some
high-grade dope here.
- I'm fine as may wine.
- Good. That's great.
You know, you should have seen
the look on your face
when you found me
in that shack.
- Looked scared as hell.
- Yeah, well, I was.
I am.
You nearly died.
Not me.
I'm going when I say I go.
- What happened, Dad?
- Nothing.
Forget about it.
Ain't no big deal.
So tell me. Boy or girl?
- How'd you know?
- Well, I ain't that far outta the loop.
Cousin Katie.
She told me you were expecting.
His name's Ben.
Is this little Ben's mama
over here?
She's purty.
No. This, uh, this is my boss.
I'm Agent Lisbon.
Why don't you tell us
what happened, Mr. Rigsby?
I gotta tell you
I could not work
for a beautiful woman like you.
It's way too distracting.
You dating anyone
right now, honey?
Both you and the victim were hit
with shotgun pellets.
Your pistol hadn't been fired
so you're not a suspect right now.
You can tell us what happened.
Years ago, I'd have probably
been too much for you.
Hell, I'd have broke you.
Now, the circumstances
I bet we move
just about the same speed.
Dad, this is serious.
You've been shot.
You need to understand
there's no more time for--
that I don't need you
or any other government
bitch fixing my problems for me.
What about Andy Huff?
He's dead.
Well, then he doesn't need anything.
The vic's business partner
should be at CBI by now.
We can talk to her,
try to get some leads.
- Rigsby.
- Yeah?
Jane and I are gonna go
talk to the barber.
- You're not working this case.
- Please, boss, I gotta do something.
- You can stay here or you can go home.
- No way. I'm not staying here.
I didn't give you a choice.
It's okay.
Go home. See your kid.
Okay.
We just wanna find whoever it is
that killed him, Ms. Stewart.
People call me Stew.
Like that matters right now.
Call me whatever.
Sorry.
This is a lot to take in.
Where did you meet the victim?
We grew up in Carson Springs.
We managed to stay
outta the gangs and the drugs.
- That put us in the minority.
- It's a rough town.
Oh, you have no idea.
Uh... we both went
to barber school.
We were buddies
so going into business together
was just a no-brainer.
This is who Huff was with.
He's an ex-con
with a violent record.
Have you seen him before?
No.
Killer wounded him but didn't go
after him when he ran away.
Like he wasn't the target.
So?
Well, we just told you
that your business partner
was driving around
with a violent criminal
and you didn't blink.
Why not?
I really don't wanna get involved.
Just tell us what you know.
You don't have to be
involved past that.
Samantha.
Please tell us what happened.
Family troubles, I guess.
We don't have any living relatives
on record.
Tom Overton was his father.
You know, the Overtons?
Overtons run Carson Springs.
Half of it, anyway.
And Tom Overton ran the family.
He died a long time ago
of cancer.
- Was Huff in the family business?
- No. No way.
Um, his mom was just a kid
when she had him.
And as soon as she saw
what kinda man Tom Overton was
she wouldn't have nothing
to do with him.
She raised him on her own
without a penny of Overton money.
She raised him honest.
Is she dead, as well?
Car crash.
None of the Overtons
even showed up at the funeral
so... no,
he wasn't close with them.
But he couldn't escape them, either?
It's family.
I mean, you know
how that is.
D.A. sent over what they could.
They've got a thick file
on Carson Springs.
The Overtons have been selling
illegal substances in town
since prohibition.
Now they focus on illegal
prescriptions and meth.
But they're not alone.
These days,
they own half the city.
The east side belongs
to a gang called the Low-Riders
that came along in the '80s.
The river that runs through town
is the border between their turfs.
That's very orderly.
The D.E.A. says the two gangs
fought a war about ten years ago.
People died. About 30.
- 30?
- Including the Overton boss.
Cutting the town in two was the only
way they would come to peace.
It's been quiet for a long time.
Huff and Steve were attacked
in Low-Rider territory.
Maybe the Low-Riders
saw him as, uh, an Overton
- decided to take him out.
- His partner said
that he had nothing to do
with the family and I believe her.
Maybe they don't care.
All's fair in war.
What war? It's been quiet
between the two gangs lately.
Why shoot someone now?
- Let's go ask them.
- We don't have enough information.
Local cops say there's a gym
where a lot of the younger gang
members hang out.
Maybe we can
learn something there.
We'll give it a shot. Cho, you and Jane
go and talk to Steve Rigsby.
He could be tied in
with one of these gangs.
- Think he'll talk?
- No.
But Jane might not need him to.
So can you tell me if the feud
between the Low-Riders
and the Overtons is heating up?
- Anything?
- Sorry, lady.
We're not allowed to talk
gang business in the gym.
It's neutral ground.
Hey, knucklehead.
You bothering this lady?
Can I help you?
Grace Van Pelt, CBI.
I'm working a case
that might have a gang angle.
Just looking
for some more information.
Fletcher Moss.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hey.
Andy Huff was murdered last night.
It's all over town. I heard that.
That's terrible.
- What happened?
- That's what we're looking into.
We're told you have a pretty
good handle on the scene here.
Any insights?
Well, you know, I heard
that he was a nice guy
uh, he was a civilian.
How come this place
is neutral ground?
Well, I started this place
about two years ago
with one rule--no gangs.
I was in gang life as a kid.
I had to get shot and go to prison
to knock some sense
into me, but, uh...
I don't know.
I figure this is a better way.
Were you an Overton
or a Low-Rider?
Neither. I was a Cobra.
Ancient history.
Andy was on Low-Rider turf
when he died.
You think they would've shot him
just for being there?
You know, back in the day
when those guys were tearing
the town apart, I'd say yeah.
But now it doesn't make
much sense.
Unless the Low-Riders are looking
to start the war up again.
You know, the Overtons
have better customers
they got better turf, less trouble.
Low-Riders may want it all.
I hate the smell of hospitals.
Everybody does.
Bad smells, bad memories.
That's because the memory
is right next to the smell box
inside your brain.
Nothing makes you remember
like a smell.
Maybe they're doing tests
or something.
Yeah, I don't think so.
Excuse me. Can I help you?
There was a man attached
to this needle.
Have you seen him?
How does a man
in his condition
walk out of a hospital
without being noticed?
He grabbed some clothes
from the man in the next room
and he walked out the door.
That's my dad.
And so Lisbon invited you
back on the case?
No, she didn't invite me.
She was reluctant, but I insisted
and she warned me to be very careful.
I-I want that clear.
Go on.
I took Cho
and we went to look for him.
I talked to some biker buddies
and an old girlfriend.
Ah, yes.
That would be the woman
called...
- "Rocket"?
- Yes.
She had heard from him.
Dad wanted to see her.
He was waiting for her
in a bar in Carson Springs
but she was scared,
so I went instead.
You went?
- Where was Cho?
- We--
I thought it was more likely
that he would come quietly
if I was alone.
He doesn't like cops.
Doesn't like anyone much.
Here you go.
Hey. Let's go.
I'm taking you back
to the hospital.
Damn. You can never trust
a woman.
Let's go.
Look, you can sit down
or you can get out
but I'm good here.
Listen, you need to be in a hospital.
I don't believe I need
to be doing a damn thing.
You have a shotgun pellet
lodged in your heart.
It could come loose
at any time.
You're just like your mother.
Worry, worry, worry.
I thought you'd be out there
looking for the guy who shot you.
I'd rather sit here and have another beer.
That's my choice.
Now you make your choice.
But I'm telling you I'm not leaving
here without a fight.
Yeah, well, I ain't fighting
you anymore.
Miss, I'll take a beer.
Hi.
Whatever it is, we're not buying.
We're not selling.
I'm Agent Lisbon, CBI.
This is Patrick Jane.
I said we're not interested.
Well, I'd love to hear that
from your boss.
That is a very nice suit on you.
Very sharp.
Whoa.
Hello.
What's his name?
- Brutus.
I'm Sue. Can I help you?
We wanted to talk to you
about Andy Huff.
And who says I'm your gal?
Well, you're the boss,
aren't you?
Dogs and humans
protect the Alpha.
Don't worry, Rawson.
It's fine. Come on.
This is my son Kyle.
Very nice to meet you, ma'am.
Sir.
Hey, Kyle.
Strapping lad.
Your brother Tom
he never claimed Huff as his son.
- Did you have any contact with him?
- Nope.
Did you kill him?
Now why would I do that?
He was my brother's...
He was my brother's blood.
I think the word
you're struggling not to say
- is "bastard."
- He was my brother's bastard.
And he never wanted anything
to do with me.
I didn't kill him.
And you don't care
that he's dead
but you do care
that he was murdered.
Appearances are a big thing
in your line of business.
My line of business?
We own some dry cleaners.
No, I'm not talking about that.
I'm talking about the drug dealing.
Drug dealing?
I don't--drug...
Huff was killed on Low-Rider turf.
Now are you involved in some
sort of dispute with the Low-Riders?
I--Low-Riders?
I'm... I...
You remember them.
They killed your husband.
I'm a businesswoman.
Dry cleaning.
I don't know who killed Huff
and I don't know why.
Your rug to dry clean, I guess.
All right, listen up. You're going
for a knockout every time, all right?
But the punch that hurts
the most is the one that lands.
You gotta hit 'em more,
not harder.
It's called the Stockton slap.
The detective's right.
All right, give me some pushups.
As many as you can do
plus 10.
That's not bad.
You watch the fights?
I've been watching some.
I like how it gets to the point.
Yeah, well, you know, with gloves
and a ref, it's not a real fight.
- In a real fight...
- Yeah, I know. I've been in a real fight.
What are you here for, detective?
My boss is on her way
to meet the Low-Riders.
I was hoping you could
help me out.
They're led by a guy
named Beltran, right?
That's a bad dude.
Overtons, uh, ran this town
for a long time
you know, and then little gangs
would pop up here and there
no threat to them.
But Beltran stood up to them.
So he killed
Sue Overton's husband?
Well, I don't know
who pulled the trigger
but yeah.
And the Overtons killed
his little brother.
That last war was brutal.
You don't want a sequel.
We're looking for Beltran.
I didn't do it.
- Do what?
- Whatever it is you think I did.
Somebody killed
a relative of the Overtons.
I sure didn't do that.
He was on your turf.
Maybe you saw Andy Huff
you wanted to send a message
to the Overtons?
A message?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
When the Overtons
beat him up
that was a message.
Question is, what was it saying?
Those bruises are only
a few days old.
Before the murder.
- Was Huff payback for the beating?
- Let's get 'em outta here.
Calm down, Joey.
I made a mistake.
I trusted the Overtons.
My guy paid for it but we didn't kill
Huff for any payback.
- What does that mean?
- We're just talking here?
Yeah, I think.
Yeah, well, there's a new
park in town.
A good place to maybe
set up a market.
You know, maybe we had
a little disagreement about it.
So the Overtons beat up your guy
over the new turf?
I say what I gotta say.
We didn't kill anybody.
Not last night.
You ever thought about just sitting
down with Sue Overton?
Having a cup of tea, little chat?
Look, in the last war
the Overtons killed my little brother.
I heard that woman Sue
ordered the hit
so, no, I am not interested
in sitting down with her, ever.
I don't want anything to do
with those people.
But if the Overtons
go to war with you
then you're--you're ready
to jump right in there?
Hell, man...
can't be no punk.
Right?
All right.
- I'm... down.
- He doesn't want to.
Somebody killed Huff to start
the feud back up.
We better do something
or this town's gonna get
real bloody real fast.
What do you think?
Did Beltran kill Huff
to provoke the Overtons
or did Sue do it
to have an excuse
to attack the Low-Riders?
- Neither.
- What do you mean, neither?
Well, Sue doesn't wanna fight
this war.
Neither does Beltran,
but they both will fight it.
- The question is, why?
- No, it's, who?
Again?
You don't like it, put your own damn
quarter in the machine.
So you're not going
after the guy who shot you?
Maybe I'm waiting for him here.
Or maybe you don't know
who he is.
Don't I?
No.
You don't.
You'd already be out there
hunting him down.
That's your code.
I don't know anything.
All I saw
were flashes in the dark.
Why were you there?
Eh, somebody called Huff.
Said they were gonna burn down
his barbershop
if he didn't come.
Kid got scared, so I went to help him.
That's all I know.
Thank you.
Let's see some pictures.
- Who's the mom?
- We're split up.
Team was working a case.
I faked my own death.
She got mad.
It's... it's complicated.
There's more pictures
if you wanna just...
I know how to use it.
- It's a hell of a thing.
- Yeah, it is.
I look at him and I feel like--
Don't go too easy on him.
No parenting advice.
Thanks.
What do you got
to complain about?
I did my job.
You did your job?
That's right.
You're still here.
You're a man of respect.
You walk around all over the place
with a legit weapon.
You got a handsome son.
I did a good job.
Yeah.
I suppose when you look
at it like that.
Damn right.
I could've drowned you
at birth.
Let's go.
Go where?
- See my grandson.
- Uh... No.
Okay, yeah.
We could do that.
You're gonna have to buy
these beers.
Huh. I'm paying, huh?
- Son...
- Hey, call 911. Right now.
Dad.
Hold on.
No. Fight it.
Come on.
Dad.
Fight. You fight it.
No!
"Ain't it a cold, cold world?"
Wayne.
Rigsby, I am so sorry.
Thanks.
We are gonna find
whoever did this.
Trust me.
Yeah.
You're on bereavement leave,
starting now.
We'll give you a call
if we catch a break in the case.
Okay.
Thanks, everyone.
Hey.
I know what you wanna do.
You can't do it.
If I got shot, he would've
found the man
who pulled the trigger
and taken care of it.
You didn't like growing up
with a dad in jail?
Ben wouldn't like it, either.
I'm sorry.
Cho's right.
Leave it to us.
Hey.
Hey. Van Pelt said that there's
no other big gangs in town.
The Overtons and the Low-Riders
drove 'em outta business.
Who told her that?
Some guy that runs a gym.
He pulls gang members
off the street.
Let me guess--
is he a former crook made good?
Yeah, I guess so.
We should pay him a visit.
Maybe she's not asking him
the right questions.
When you step in that cage
you'll be fighting
for your life.
I'm not gonna put you in that cage
unless you're properly armed.
These are your weapons.
Right now, I'm teaching you
how to fire your weapons.
Three-round burst.
There you go.
Get your shoulder up.
Get the shoulder up on the jab.
There you go.
Come on.
Give me some.
Fletcher Moss?
Hi, I'm Agent Lisbon with the CBI.
This is Patrick Jane.
- Hey. Good.
- How you doing?
Agent Van Pelt said
you were really helpful.
What can I do for you?
Well, it's quite a setup
you have here.
Yeah, you know, I'm just trying
to give these guys
a little place to go
before they get in too deep.
We think Huff's death
might trigger another war
between the Overtons
and the Low-Riders.
Is there a third player in town
that might be behind it?
- No. Those...
- Well, actually, we're thinking--
well, I'm--I'm thinking
someone ought to just sit down
with these two gangs
and have them talk it out.
What do you say?
That's nuts.
Low-Riders killed Sue's husband.
Overtons killed Beltran's little brother.
Those guys hate each other.
They're not sitting down
across from each other, ever.
This gym is neutral territory, right?
So what if we held the meeting here?
But they're not talking,
so you'd be wasting your time.
It's worth a try.
If I can arrange it
would you be okay if we held
that meeting right here?
Could save a lot of lives.
- Go ahead. Try.
- Thank you.
What was that about?
We need to get back
to the Overtons.
Uh, actually, I'll go alone.
- You're a little too cop.
- Too cop?
Van Pelt. Yeah.
I need to get something delivered
to Carson Springs.
No, doesn't matter what it is
as long as it's big, heavy,
and on the back of a truck.
Okay. Call me
when you're done. Bye.
I thought we'd said our piece
to each other.
And I thought it was about time
we started talking straight.
I have a proposition.
There's a Low-Rider
that's ready to give up
his gang to the CBI.
Whole gang.
But he needs to know that when
the other Low-Riders go down
you will give him a job.
Why should I trust you?
Well, I'm not asking you
to do anything illegal
I'm just saying
you'll give the guy a job.
Doing what, I don't--
I don't need to know.
This is a bunch of crap.
The Low-Riders have ordered
a substantial supply of guns.
The supplier's supposed to arrive
at noon today.
- What kind of guns?
- I don't know.
I-I know nothing about guns.
All I'm asking
is that you check it out.
If the information is correct,
you give this guy a shot.
I wanna meet him.
I wanna see
this informant in the flesh.
Yes, well, that could
be difficult.
I wanna meet him,
or there's no deal!
Okay. Well...
Well, I will see what I can do.
Check out this gun business.
From a distance.
It's 12:30. They're not getting
any shipment.
So that cop wasn't on the level?
He seem on the level to you?
- No.
- This is a waste of time.
Son of a bitch.
There it is.
Call Sue. Let her know.
Okay. So they're out there.
They're spying on me.
So what?
Well, it means our informant
in the Overtons is telling the truth.
So he's part of their family?
And he'll give them all up
as long as I promise
- to hook him up afterwards?
- That's the deal.
I wanna meet him.
- Uh, I don't know.
- Then forget it.
Okay.
Well, I'll see what I can do.
Hey, boss.
There's some dude out back
with a flatbed full of scrap metal.
What?
I gotta take that.
I, uh...
I'll set up the meeting
and I'll get back to you, okay?
Hey, guys!
Glad you could make it.
Follow me.
This better not be
a waste of my time.
We're not off
to the greatest of starts.
What are you doing here?
Has it started yet?
It's happening right now.
You should be at home.
- I'm here.
- You sure?
Yeah.
They should all be
in the office by now.
Thanks.
All right. Everybody settle down.
We're not gonna do this here.
I thought you said
you were gonna bust them.
Yeah, well, uh, I-I told them
exactly the same thing
about you.
Uh, big lie on my part.
I'm sorry.
Just needed to get the two of you
in a room together.
- Why?
- To stop the feud
before anyone else gets killed.
- You know Moss?
- Listen, my gym is neutral ground.
You're safe here.
He's very good at talking kids
outta making dumb decisions
and, let's face it
you guys are acting
like a couple of kids.
- A sit-down.
- That's the idea. Give it a try.
If it doesn't work, go nuts
shoot each other all you like
just not when I'm there.
What the hell?
Let's go. Let 'em talk.
Okay.
You lie, woman.
That park was open turf.
Then we send my guy down there
your boys jumped him.
Open turf?
That park is mine.
So you paid a price
for trespassing
and you kill my nephew
for payback?
I know for a fact you pulled
that trigger yourself.
You are one crazy old lady.
You scum could never
learn your place.
- I have given you the east--
- You ain't given me nothing!
Okay?
Who told you I pulled the trigger
on your nephew?
This isn't how you do it.
We're here to talk about peace
not dwell on he said-she said.
Let's--let's dwell on it.
It's all very good.
You're doing a lot of talking
you're not doing a lot of listening.
Let's take the park situation.
Beltran, you said
that it was open turf.
Who told you that?
I got my sources.
Well, in this case,
your source was wrong, huh?
Who's your source?
That's none of your business.
And who told you for a fact
that Beltran killed Huff?
Damn.
- Son of a bitch.
- Bingo.
Now when you two criminal geniuses
are done killing each other
Mr. Moss here and his new gang
are ready to take over.
Son of a bitch.
You killed my nephew,
and you blamed it on Beltran.
Son of a bitch!
You've got this wrong.
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
Drop the weapon!
Police!
Do it now!
I can't move, man.
I can't feel my arms.
Please get me some help.
Help me. Please help me.
I said I can't move!
Steven Rigsby says "hi."
You'll get my report
when I'm finished.
Until then, you will continue
with your paid suspension.
You're free to go.
You're gonna regret this someday.
- What?
- Well, this. This paperwork.
Every night you just file it
and forget it.
You know--you know what it's like?
It's like...
cooking a beautiful meal
and putting it straight
in the refrigerator...
forever.
You could help.
No, I couldn't.
So... what's your report
gonna say?
It will say that Agent Rigsby
acted appropriately
and with sound judgment
when he used lethal force against Moss.
Good work.
- You got away with it.
- Me?
Well, I can't make a case
but you chose a remote location
for the meeting
you set up a situation
where Moss had to flee.
And there, by chance,
was Rigsby.
Well, I'm--I'm flattered.
You--you flatter me, but, uh...
I can't take credit for that.
Moss didn't have to run.
I would've brought him in.
The plan did require Moss to put
his own head in the noose.
Small gamble
Jane had to make
to keep everyone's
hands clean.
- Moss fired his gun.
- So you all say.
And of course,
Moss can't tell his version.
And now Rigsby has taken
perfectly legal revenge
against the man
who killed his father.
Do you think it will affect him?
Well, I think it's better to regret
something you did
than something you...
didn't do.
Perhaps.
I suppose Rigsby will never know.
Agent Lisbon,
my report will reflect
that you made a mistake
in calling Agent Rigsby to the scene.
An error in judgment.
Yes, sir, it was.
- Yeah, Lisbon didn't call Rigsby. I did.
- Jane.
Of course you did.
Agent Lisbon, your instincts to protect
your team are admirable.
And your biggest flaw.
Yes, well, we all have our flaws.
Don't we, Agent LaRoche?
"I might have to leave you"
"I think is what she said"
"I wish I could sleep
'stead of tossing in bed"
"I can find myself thinking
that I'd rather be dead"
It's okay.
"'Cause ain't it a cold, cold world?"
"Ain't it a cold, cold world?"